hello
my name is green and welcome back to
another episode of hermitcraft and today
we are working on sahara again
the build hasn't actually moved very far
since the last episode but i'm hoping to
get a bit of work done the redstone on
the other hand has been done for the
most part i
have to be honest with all of you guys
i'm not entirely sure what all of this
stuff does
i think this is where the items are
stored for the the shop so each one of
these little modules is where one of the
items so maybe this one takes care of
dirt grass cobble whatever it is we're
selling they're in here
and then some magic happens and then it
ends up over by the shop front
i'm
not really sure
i'll tell you what i've been doing
though i've made a little room with
parrots in so that i can dance
yeah those guys were busy doing redstone
and
this this is
this is what the inside of my mind looks
like
[Music]
yeah
i think we're going to keep this room in
here
[Laughter]
but one thing that has appeared is this
thing up here and it looks like a
telescope
going off into the distance
so let's go and take a look at what we
can see
wait is that
is that poultry man
on the beach
huh
that's weird
he's having a barbecue
with his chicken friends
well at least he's having fun wherever
he is off in the
maybe poultry man left this for me
i think maybe we should check upon him
every now and again see what's going on
i guess this is poultry man's way of
letting me know that he's a-okay having
a great time on some beach far away but
we have more important things to do than
to worry about what poultry man's up to
because this is very empty and seeing as
those modules are now complete
it kind of falls on me to finish up the
rest of this build the only problem is
i'm not really sure what i need to do
anymore but we've had some other news
regarding the jangla so let's head over
to baker street and find out
doc actually messaged me on discord and
says there's been a bit of a jangler
development so i'm guessing that he's
been over but he said he wanted to meet
me at baker street meeting me in my own
office is
a little bit rude don't you think anyway
they should be waiting for me now
[Music]
sherlock yep they're there
hello hi oh i'm not sure look hold on
hold on hold on just you know avert your
eyes about your eyes
one second
well hello
hello sir back to business dachshund and
scooby-doo
yes yes yes yes so what's going on
what's happened what's the development
did he did he fall for the the trap
well we sold
question is nobody left yeah i'll show
you come on all right let's go we sold
all right yeah we sold out yeah well but
how do we i mean great now we made
diamonds still don't know who the
jungler is i mean good platforms
i mean we've gotten rich but we haven't
really solved the crime
so we have
we have sold the solve the crime
honestly
he took the bait but the diamonds were
not what we were after although i i
guess we could share these diamonds um
no actually i'll take the diamonds
um anyway uh what we've got here is not
just 27 diamonds what we have here is
conclusive evidence
that i know who the jungler is and i've
been suspicious of it ever since we went
to the flying cookie i'm going to do a
big reveal for you okay you ready for
this we're going to go through all of
the clues and hints that have led me to
this conclusion and then i will see what
you think
so let me take us back to the beginning
at the start the jungler returned the
diamonds which is a good deed which led
me to believe that this was a good
person at heart
then that led us to the second jangle
which was a flying cookie as we all
remember with the red herring of leading
you to stress what interested me wasn't
actually
the riddle or anything like that it was
the way that the cookie was built it
used so many slabs and staircases really
really well that was a beautiful flying
cookie and it's not the same style that
stress would use
but it was well lit which threw me off a
little bit
but then
we had another jangle the jungler shop
appeared and he left a clue in my office
with a peter pan reference by the exit
yeah that was hilarious potentially
a disney fan
then
we went down into the jungle shop
and it was well built this time not well
lit and by this point i'm nearly 99 sure
i know who it is but then as you know
we laid this trap and to prove that this
was a trap here's a little clip of us
talking about it or at least me telling
these two what it was
before we make this cookie shop guys i
have a theory and it's just that a
theory
so
what i'm thinking we do
is that we don't put this particular
part
in the video because the jangler is 100
watching our videos yeah yeah definitely
here's the real plan when we make this
cookie shop
we're going to make it terribly we're
going to make a really awful build
because i have a suspicion who it is and
if they change some of the build or the
surrounding area i will be
absolutely sure who it is and then we
can
confront them and i'm not going to put
it by you guys because i know that
you're just going to go straight for him
and it might be it might be wrong
so the whole point was that this cookie
wasn't supposed to be about getting
diamonds at all
we intentionally well i intentionally
made sure that this lawn here was pretty
awful because i knew
i knew that if good times with scar
was the jangler and he came here with
the diamonds he would not be able to
help himself but fix it because we
plonked this at cherry on purpose
because i believed it was good times
with the jungler
elementary scooby-doo you're a genius
yes
i mean that literally just blew my mind
yeah that was amazing so i'm now 100
sure this is conclusive evidence that it
was scar the whole time
and he's been playing us and it makes
sense because scar's such a good guy he
wouldn't be doing some bad pranks of
course he's going to give cookies to us
yeah and he gave our diamonds back to us
and exactly so this is really awkward i
think yeah i think he probably just uh
he just wanted to return the diamonds
yeah i blame you doc
wait what me
what did i do
exist
well either way now that we know he's
the jungler we've definitely got to go
and confront him about it but i think i
think we've got i mean scar's gone
massive on this assuming that it is scar
he's gone well overboard from what i
could possibly imagine this would become
so i think we've got to reveal well
confront him in the best way possible so
i think we should go and do a big
jangler build on top of his base in some
kind of way and then just point him in
the direction and then get get in a call
with him and just go like we know it's
you
dachshund and dogson i think we've done
it i think this shouts
jangler if i ever saw a giant yes what
do you think it's well by we you mean
you
yeah okay
these
ren watched doc made the the concrete
for me but
i think this is absolutely bright i got
a green guy come on man
the only issue is that it looks great
from here and i think this is probably
where we need to talk to scar because if
you
fly around
it doesn't look that great from the rest
of the angles it doesn't look great at
all the green one is flopping in the
kind of wrong direction but
there's a strong breeze coming from the
back you know
yeah
so it only looks good from this little
nether portal island here but
it's so difficult to make this sort of
thing look good from all angles so yeah
as long as we talk to scar from here i
think this is great so now we've just
got to wait for him to to see it and
then he's going to know what's up like
like yeah
oh
there he is
oh hey guys uh and dog how are you all
doing good yeah it has jelly right here
yeah i guess
have you seen have you seen this yeah
yeah
jeez i guess the jungler was around huh
it
[Music]
she busted me she busted me even my own
cat
yeah are you the jangla scar
yes
sherlock green you cracked the case
buddy oh we did it
he did it
yeah it ain't bad though you know scar i
mean honestly bro you should have just
told me you got the diamonds man yeah
again into this craziness last time that
escalated into a war like this time it's
only jester head so come on try to avoid
the war doc i was trying to avoid it so
i would like to commend you on your
amazing clues they were very smart and
yeah
we we struggled but sherlock green
cracked a number of them so wait what
what was it was it actually a typo
we all yeah to know
was this a plan or did you actually just
mess up and write i mean i mean i could
say it was a plan and feel good about
myself but i would be lying i'd be lying
[Laughter]
it nice
an awesome adventure though so that
could be yeah it certainly was i ended
up did you enjoy the cookies
by the way oh man yeah the cookies were
the best
i've ended up being the scooby-doo of
the group and
i think it's only appropriate that we
take the meme to its full closure so all
right yeah could you please put this on
there you go
there we go
okay
it wasn't etho the whole time it was
good times with the jungler what and i
could have got it could have gone away
with it for you meddling kids and dog
i'm out of here
[Music]
yes
well renson and doxon
we we need to go and settle
payment because this this so this case
has been solved oh
there's payment involved
well
yeah
i didn't start this shop to just for fun
diamonds i'm poor i thought we were just
hanging out as mates you know just as
buddies
man
how much do you want
how long did it take me to solve this
case
a week
yeah
um
64 diamonds so we'll call it eaten you
got your diamonds back from four
diamonds
here take half of that and then
rip
it would be worth it though you give it
giving me fake diamonds what fake giving
me fake sirens
you think i can't read look at this
diamonds
that's the more
yeah
i don't
i don't encounter it i don't deal in
counterfeit diamonds you're all done
thanks green it's been real we'll smell
you uh
give me real diamonds
i want real diamonds i'll get you
don't don't eat don't you even
you you come back here
it's a good time to pitch my
you just died shulker box to you
oh you oh
[Laughter]
seriously though sherlock green thanks
my dude for solving the case we were
just pulling your leg on the diamonds
man yeah yeah take these
fake diamonds back
also i've got a little bit of a gift for
you to thank you for the solving the
crime for us my dude here you go this is
for you enjoy
you're puffy you're very young oh
pufferfish yeah do within what you will
i think i should put him in here yeah
that that'll that'll do very nicely
he'll be very happy in there but uh yeah
that was really fun thank you g for a
wonderful little mystery and uh puffy's
now got a wonderful little home nice
the case has been solved good times with
scar has been
outed as the janky
jerry do you think he's going to
continue being the jank probably not
right
it's not really a secret anymore isn't
it oh yeah i will tell you you know i
saw zuma going into his shop and
actually placing an order so i guess
he's in business now
yep
um but yeah gee we're gonna chill out
green we're gonna love and leave you
we've got some diamonds to burn my dude
yeah so what why are you burning
diamonds uh we don't want to talk about
it well
they don't even ask that's
it's just sad bye bye bye
bye
so that pretty much concludes our jangla
story i'm guessing that scar's
definitely not going to keep this hat
because it does look brilliant actually
and it's not as bad as i thought from
every single angle but there's some like
like this one or it just doesn't look
quite right
but i think this was a brilliant way
to out him as the jungler and oh my
goodness kudos to scarf was such an
amazing goose chase that he sent us on i
absolutely loved it but now that the
case has closed we need to move on to
doing other things now hopefully someone
will come up with a new mystery for
sherlock green to take on but there are
a few other mysteries abound but i have
actually been working on the sahara
project a bit more and i'm stuck i'm
honestly really really stumped as to how
to detail some of this stuff because
this is looking pretty plain i feel like
it's moving in the right direction
but at the same time
something's not right and sometimes when
you're building and i do this quite
often i just stop building for a minute
and just sort of let my mind process and
envision and evaluate what is going to
look the best for it sometimes it goes
really wrong and i have to redo the
whole thing
other times i just get it right first
time and those those are my favorite
excuse me
but
he wasn't there a second ago i think
this side looks particularly plain just
everything about this part of the build
doesn't really match up with the style
yet but don't worry i'm going to come up
with something and probably re-tackle it
i was thinking over here for example
that we have a little ledge like maybe
that there's a tiny little office space
here like maybe just a small meeting
room with a couple of tables and chairs
in here and then you can see over there
so maybe like you know me me and this
gal and mumbo we're we're conducting
business here and we can see the
customers come in and we can we can
watch but like i said there's still a
lot of detailing that needs to be done
here
and then we've got all of our supply
problems we haven't even got all the
resources to make everything yet we've
got farms for a lot of the blocks but
things like concrete we're just not
there yet we need more sand we need more
gravel and we need more dyes and then
how we're going to create all the
concrete as well i feel like that's
going to be a big seller but we've got a
long way to go now hopefully i can come
up with some stuff later on i'm pretty
sure the design will come to me in a few
days and i really really want to move on
with sahara faster and faster because i
feel like concorp are definitely up to
something and sahara needs to get
selling some products very very soon
but actually i thought about it and i
haven't actually checked my shop in a
little while
and i heard that i'd sold out so if
that's true which it is we have got some
diamonds finally
we've made plenty of diamonds today oh
my goodness
we've made a stack and a half of
diamonds in one day that's pretty good
going and there seems to be a few
pickles lying around for some reason
someone's obviously dropping pickles in
the shopping district wow there's a real
there's a lot of them
what the heck
someone is
they're everywhere someone is dropping a
lot of pickles is there any more
there's seriously a lot of pickles going
on so let's pop the diamonds in here and
we've got nearly four stacks of diamonds
this is absolutely brilliant i haven't
been this rich since jeven gave me all
of those diamonds but i think that is
all that i have time for today everybody
uh this video is a little bit shorter
than normal but i've got a lot of stuff
to be getting on with i think maybe we
should just check in on the old poultry
man just before we leave
so let's head back up into the telescope
and see what he's doing
looking out over the ocean it looks like
he's having a great time and that's what
matters so thank you very much for
watching everyone as always and i will
see you in the next video good
bye
[Music]
yeah i bet you thought i was gonna drop
there didn't you huh
predictable
bye everyone